{
  "level": 2,
  "unit": 4,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ my hair after my bath.",
          "answer": "comb"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ falls when the boy eats a cookie.",
          "answer": "crumb"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "That is a funny _____________ in the play!",
          "answer": "scene"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A dog found them by tracking their _____________.",
          "answer": "scent"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ is buzzing by my ear!",
          "answer": "gnat"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "What does that street _____________ say?",
          "answer": "sign"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mom will use this sharp _____________ to cut the carrots.",
          "answer": "knife"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you _____________ the way to the library?",
          "answer": "know"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Pablo wears a watch on his left _____________.",
          "answer": "wrist"
        },
        { "prompt": "Rachel likes _____________ poems.", "answer": "writing" },
        {
          "prompt": "This box is in the shape of a _____________.",
          "answer": "cube"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Rebecca loves to listen to _____________.",
          "answer": "music"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ throw the ball in the house.",
          "answer": "Don't"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I will _____________ a sandwich for lunch.",
          "answer": "eat"
        },
        { "prompt": "Those elephants are _____________ big.", "answer": "very" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ put money in a cash register.",
          "answer": "clerk"
        },
        { "prompt": "The _____________ of cows grazed.", "answer": "herd" },
        {
          "prompt": "Daniel was _____________ in the race.",
          "answer": "first"
        },
        { "prompt": "Jenny has on a blue _____________ .", "answer": "skirt" },
        { "prompt": "Mom helped me _____________ the soup.", "answer": "stir" },
        {
          "prompt": "It was hard to _____________ the butter.",
          "answer": "churn"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Sammy _____________ his ankle when he fell.",
          "answer": "hurt"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The water balloon _____________ when it hit the ground.",
          "answer": "burst"
        },
        { "prompt": "I have a lot of _____________ to do.", "answer": "work" },
        {
          "prompt": "I think rain is _____________ than snow.",
          "answer": "worse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you _____________ where the playground is?",
          "answer": "know"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I wear a bracelet on my _____________ .",
          "answer": "wrist"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Andrea _____________ her shoe under the couch.",
          "answer": "found"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "This letter is _____________ my grandfather.",
          "answer": "from"
        },
        { "prompt": "My birthday is _____________ .", "answer": "today" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The ship sailed into the _____________ .",
          "answer": "port"
        },
        { "prompt": "What city is _____________ of here?", "answer": "north" },
        { "prompt": "Jake wants _____________ rice.", "answer": "more" },
        {
          "prompt": "Dad went to the _____________ for milk.",
          "answer": "store"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mark used the _____________ to turn the boat.",
          "answer": "oar"
        },
        { "prompt": "Listen to that lion _____________ !", "answer": "roar" },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you write the answer on the _____________ ?",
          "answer": "board"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Carl put a new _____________ in the car.",
          "answer": "part"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "What time does school _____________ ?",
          "answer": "start"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We like to play in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "park"
        },
        { "prompt": "_____________ , letâ€™s play a game.", "answer": "First" },
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ my toe when I kicked the ball.",
          "answer": "hurt"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Dinosaurs lived a long time _____________ .",
          "answer": "ago"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Would you please _____________ my backpack?",
          "answer": "carry"
        },
        { "prompt": "Many _____________ live in our town.", "answer": "people" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I _____________ you to run a mile.", "answer": "dare" },
        {
          "prompt": "The cats _____________ at the birds outside the window.",
          "answer": "stare"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "How much is the _____________ to ride the bus?",
          "answer": "fare"
        },
        { "prompt": "Leah has dark brown _____________ .", "answer": "hair" },
        {
          "prompt": "Joe put on a _____________ of warm boots.",
          "answer": "pair"
        },
        { "prompt": "The _____________ has a hard seat.", "answer": "chair" },
        {
          "prompt": "They saw a black _____________ in the forest.",
          "answer": "bear"
        },
        { "prompt": "Beth ate a juicy _____________ .", "answer": "pear" },
        { "prompt": "_____________ is my homework?", "answer": "Where" },
        {
          "prompt": "I left my notebook over _____________ .",
          "answer": "there"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mandy has a _____________ friend named Sue.",
          "answer": "dear"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Listen to those loud _____________ from the crowd!",
          "answer": "cheers"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Randy _____________ how to spell all the words.",
          "answer": "knew"
        },
        { "prompt": "I _____________ flew on an airplane.", "answer": "never" },
        {
          "prompt": "My friends and I _____________ on the school bus.",
          "answer": "talk"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "The baby panda is very __________ !", "answer": "cute" },
        {
          "prompt": "Joan put an ice __________ in her drink.",
          "answer": "cube"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Can you smell the __________ from the fire?",
          "answer": "fumes"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We listen to __________ on the radio.",
          "answer": "music"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The class is studying a __________ on energy.",
          "answer": "unit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Martin will order lunch from the __________ .",
          "answer": "menu"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There are a __________ birds in the tree.",
          "answer": "few"
        },
        { "prompt": "The family sits in the __________ .", "answer": "pew" },
        {
          "prompt": "How much __________ does the car need?",
          "answer": "fuel"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The actor uses __________ to learn his lines.",
          "answer": "cues"
        },
        { "prompt": "Can I ride the __________ ?", "answer": "pony" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ sits on her throne.", "answer": "queen" },
        {
          "prompt": "We __________ dance lessons last week.",
          "answer": "began"
        },
        { "prompt": "Will you __________ to my party?", "answer": "come" },
        {
          "prompt": "They __________ presents to their friends.",
          "answer": "give"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
